姑娘们  我做了个重大决定
Girls, I have made a big decision.
你决定要去变性了吗
You're having a sex change?
我完全支持你  但阿憨你得小心
I totally support you, but be careful, Han.
女变男手术不容易呢
Female to male is very tricky.
你是过来人  当然很了解
Well, you would know.
哎哟
Me-ow!
吃了术前荷尔蒙  就是不一样啊
He must have already started on the hormones.
这就是我的重大决定
Now, here's my big decision.
我们要从黏糊糊玻璃番茄酱瓶
We're moving from those icky glass ketchup bottles
改换到现代的新塑料挤压瓶
to modern, new squeeze bottles.
哇靠  好前无古人后无来者的"创意"
Wow, that is some fresh, outside-the-box thinking.
我们像1976年苹果的实习生一样见证传奇啊
It's like being an intern at Apple during the summer of '76.
没错  请叫我"憨布斯"[手交]
That's right. Call me "Han Jobs."
你放心  我绝对只叫你"含布斯"
Oh, I will only call you "Han Jobs."
真不敢相信大家都走人了
I can't believe everybody else is gone,
我们还得留下弄这些
and we're stuck here doing this.
这有一股超浓的毒塑料味
Eew, this has a really toxic plastic smell.
快给我
Give me that.
麦克斯  你在吸番茄酱罐气吗
Max, are you huffing a ketchup bottle?
希望这毒气能杀了我脑中那些能记得
I'm hoping it kills the brain cells that'll remember
我周五夜还得留下弄番茄酱罐的脑细胞
I'm stuck doing ketchups on a friday night.
麦克斯  拿来
Max, give it to me!
不管你信不信  你没这么堕落凄惨
Whether you believe it or not, you're above that.
而且其实我们都没这么凄惨
And you know what? We're above this.
别弄这玩意了  出去玩吧
Forget this. Let's go out.
我刚恢复单身  而你又来者不拒对吧
I mean, I'm newly single, and you're not picky.
没错
True.
我准备好要放松一下
I'm ready to let my hair down
去享受个尽情欢乐
and have one of those crazy
又不乱花钱的夜晚了
yet fiscally responsible kind of nights.
你是指趁别的女人去上厕所时
You mean steal other girls' drinks
偷喝掉人家酒的狂欢夜吗
when they go to the bathroom?
说真的啦  如果只有不到20块
Seriously, what can you do in Williamsburg
在威廉斯堡这一带可以玩啥啊
if you have less than $20?
可以漂漂亮亮得"站在街边"  直到35岁
Hang out on the sidewalk and look good till you turn 35.
然后跟你的朋友说"我得搬家了"
Then turn to your friends and say, "I have to move home."
对了  你知道吗
Hey, you know what?
那个丹麦乐团在马具匠酒吧表演呢
The Raveonettes are playing the lorimer lounge.
我们有少少的钱与多多的胸器
We got a little tip money and lot of deez.
就等着见证奇迹吧
So let's just watch the magic unfold.
我上次看他们的现场演出
I haven't seen The Raveonettes live
都还是当年在丹麦呢
since I saw them in Denmark.
这也太巧了吧  我第一次听到他们
That is crazy because I first heard of them
是我与阿"麦"  在他房里[丹]厮混的那会呢
when I was dry-humping a guy named Mark in his den,
咱真是同"命"相怜啊
So...twinsies!
我真是凤凰变麻雀了啊
Wow, my life has really changed.
我上次身处舞厅后巷是为了避人群狗仔
The last time I was in an alley behind a club,
当时还跟奥尔森姐妹的其中一个一起躲车上呢
I was in an SUV with one of the Olsen twins.
我还是没认出是姐姐还是妹妹
I still don't know which one.
说到奥尔森姐妹
Hey, speaking of the Olsen twins,
我有次醉倒  在花园地精旁醒来呢
I once woke up next to a garden gnome.
咱们的计划可真"成功"啊
Well, so much for our plan.
胸器依旧在  但是没有票
Yes, we've still got "doze," but no tickets.
肯定有办法可以进去的
There's gotta be a way for us to get in.
你们好啊  美女们
What up, ladies?
你好  哞先生  随便啦
Hi. Moo. Whatever.
你们想要票吗
You need tickets?
贝西[常见牛名]  我们可能有兴趣哦
Well, Bessie, we might be interested.
多少钱
How much?
如果金发妹愿意帮我"挤奶"  就免费送
You can have 'em for free if the blonde one milks me.
卡洛琳  你想要票的决心有多少呢
How bad do you want those tickets, Caroline?
没那么想要
Ha, not that bad.
再见  哞先生  随便啦
Bye. Moo. Whatever.
抱歉  麦克斯  但我真没办法
Sorry, Max, but I can't come back
去拉陌生男子的奶头
from pulling a strange man's teats.
你这么觉得
You think that,
等你真拉下去  其实也没那么差啦
and then you do it, and it's not so bad.
在纽约  没钱就没奇迹
Wow, New York without money is like no magic.
有钱没钱  奇迹还是到处都有的好吗
There's magic all over the city with or without money.
只是你得自己创造而已
You just have to make your own.
喝了就有奇迹了
By drinking.
包包牌啤酒吗
Oh. Purse beer.
抱歉没有包包牌玉米脆片
Sorry there's no purse nachos.
我全吃光了
I ate them all.
顶多就是嘛...
Best I can do is, uh,
包里我避孕丸下方那块还有点起司碎
the cheese dust down near the birth control.
这也太悲催了
Okay, this is ratchet.
我们站在这像俩傻逼白人妞似地
We're just standing here like a couple of beckys.
说好的奇迹呢
Where's your magic now?
想看奇迹吗
Oh, you wanna see magic?
妈咪妈咪哄
Abracadabra.
让我进去  傻逼们
Let me in, dumbos.
妈咪他妈咪的哄
Abra-ca-damn-dabra!
我不知道那垃圾桶跟你说了什么
You know, I don't know what that trash bin said to you,
但我觉得你们很般配
but you make a cute couple.
你俩要是没挨到
I think it'd be a shame to break up
看见爱情结晶的那天  我觉得会很可惜呢
before you got to see what your kids would look like.
这几年的确是不太顺遂
Well, it's been a rough couple of years for us,
我考虑读研究所
what with me considering grad school
而他就只当个垃圾桶  但我能说啥
and him being a trash can, but what can I say?
-这就是爱嘛  -我明白
- It's love. - I understand.
美国人最爱垃圾了
Americans love their garbage.
不然你怎么解释为啥会有
How else would you explain
真实主妇各地版的这些烂节目
The real housewives of everything?
你们欧洲版的迪士尼乐园  也得感谢我们
You're welcome for euro Disney, by the way.
我叫格汉  跟乐队一起的
My name's Graham. I'm with the band.
我叫麦克斯  跟金发妞一起的
Max. I'm with the blonde.
有兴趣的话  你们可以来后台玩玩啊
You two can come and hang backstage if you like.
你男朋友就继续留外面被人骂[丢垃圾]吧
Your boyfriend can stay outside and get trashed.
悲催傻逼白人妞  进来吧
Hey, ratchet-ass becky, we're in.
厄尔  我好担心哦
Earl, I'm worried.
麦克斯昨晚跟那男的一起走后就没消息了
I haven't seen Max since she left with that guy last night.
我都打给她几百次了
I've called her a million times.
她就接过一次
She picked up once,
她当时要么是在做爱  要么就是在跟熊打架
and she was either having sex or fighting a bear.
不用担心  麦克斯不会有危险的
Don't you worry. Max can take care of herself.
我看过她用意念  把挡路的卡车给推开呢
I once saw her push a truck out of her way with her mind.
大家好啊
Hey, everybody.
抱歉
Hey. Pardon.
抱歉我有点凌乱
Pardon my appearance,
但我刚才在公园里
but I was just in the park
追着高中男子田径队的后面跑呢
running after the high school boys' track team.
我跟她说我不会介意
I told her it was fine with me.
我料她也追不上任何一个
I know she will never catch one of them.
那你就错了
Oh, says you.
布兰登要带我一起去学校舞会呢
I'm going to the prom with Brandon.
只要他爸借车给他  他就带我去
Yeah, if his--if his dad will lend him the car.
苏菲  我爱死你穿这套衣服了
Sophie, I always love when you wear that outfit.
让我好想上了你这"仙纳杜"
It makes me wanna xana-do you.
大家好咩
'Sup?
古德拜啊
Pip-pip and cheerio.
谢天谢地  我都要担心死了
Max, thank God. I was so worried.
等等  你怎么今天看起来特别美啊
Wait, why do you look extra pretty?
估计是这副免费入手的眼镜的功劳
Probably the new shades I didn't pay for.
或归功于他"舌炖"了我底下的"庄园"吧
Or the hours of him going downton on my abbey.
别说了  不许剧透
Hold up. No spoilers.
我还没看第三季呢
I haven't started season three yet.
-厄尔  你看《唐顿庄园》啊  -对啊
- Earl, you watch that show? - Yes, I do.
由白人演佣人的剧我都爱看
I enjoy any show where the help is white.
所以你跟那男的"睡"了吗
So you slept with that guy?
我"大睡特睡"了他一番
Oh, I really slept with that guy.
做得好啊  小姑娘
You go, girl.
不达高潮  誓不罢休
Don't stop till you get enough!
真没想到你会待整夜
I'm surprised you spent the night.
你不都是在他们发现钱被偷光前
Don't you usually leave before they realize
就赶紧溜之大吉了吗
there's nothing in their wallet?
你昨晚还在抱怨没奇迹了
Last night you were complaining about no magic.
而我今早起床  能欣赏窗外中央公园美景
Then I woke up this morning to a view of the park
还有肉桂卷吃
and hot cinnamon rolls.
我现在来餐厅上班  肚里还满满的肉桂卷
Now I'm back at the diner but full of cinnamon rolls.
看  这就是奇迹  吃土吧  刘谦
Boom. Magic. Suck it, David Blaine.
你玩得开心就好  我昨晚唯一开心的
Well, at least you had fun. The only fun I had last night
就只有趁那个乳牛哥醉倒时  绊了他
was when that cow dude passed out on his feet,
让他摔个牛吃屎
and I tipped him over.
-你之后还会跟他见面吗  -周日
- So are you gonna see him again? - Sunday.
我知道你没钱后就没听过这几个字
And I realize you haven't heard these words
但是我还是要告诉你  "你也有受邀哦"
since you lost your money, but you're invited.
你是要邀请我去当你们那
So you're asking me to be the third wheel
"两"夜情的电灯泡吗
on a two-night one-night stand?
所以私人专机跟两张去洛杉矶的
So I guess a private plane and two tickets
格莱美奖门票也吸引不了你吗
to the Grammys in L.A. won't do it for you either?
我们受邀了  你个小贱人
'Cause, bitch, we're invited!
格莱美奖吗  太棒了吧
The Grammys? That's so exciting.
我现在好需要被人误认为是
Oh, and my self-esteem could really use
泰勒·斯威夫特来提升一下自尊心
being mistaken for Taylor Swift right now.
也代表我现在自尊真是低到爆了
Which tells you how low my self-esteem is.
那男的要派私人飞机接我呢
The guy is sending a private plane for me.
私人飞机啊
A private plane!
知道我床上功夫多棒了吧
That's how good I am in bed.
我们要去参加格莱美奖啦
We're going to the Grammys!
你们在兴奋什么啊
What is all of the excitement?
阿憨  我们周末得请假
Han, we need the weekend off.
我们要去参加格莱美奖
We're going to the Grammys.
格莱美奖  真的格莱美奖典礼吗
The Grammys? On the real-real?
你觉得你会见到二链子吗
Do you think you'll meet 2 Chainz?
他是我的好兄弟呢
That's my boi!
才不是呢  他明明是我的好兄弟
No, he can't be your boi, he's my boi.
二链子屌爆了  他唱了我心中的神曲呢
2 Chainz is the man. He sings my anthem.
"我们代表棒棒糖公会"吗
We represent the lollipop guild?
是他那首唱"大屁股妞"的歌啦
I'm talking about his ode to big booty hos.
生日歌是我的歌好吗
Birthday song is my song.
屁  生日歌是我的主打歌好吗
No, birthday song is my song.
每天早上洗澡时我都哼唧着
Every morning in the shower I rap
* 我生日就要个大屁股骚妞玩玩 *
* All I want for my birthday is a big booty ho *
你学黑人不成  还更像脑残白人了
Wow, that actually makes you look whiter.
我可以让你们周末请假
I'll give you the weekend off
但是你们得让他在我的演唱会T恤上签名
if you get him to sign my concert T-shirt.
我们永远遇不到他的吧  不过没问题
Well, we're never gonna meet him, but done.
我的美梦要实现啦
All my dreams are coming true!
好兴奋哦
This is so exciting.
我终于要上飞机耍耍啦
I am finally going a plane ride.
麦克斯  你没坐过飞机吗
Max, you've never been on a plane?
是啊  没坐过
I've never been on a plane.
连蛇都坐过飞机了好吗[电影《飞机上有蛇》]
Max, even snakes have been on a plane.
早安啊  女士  欢迎登机
Good morning, madame. Welcome aboard.
今天是个飞行的好日子  对吧
It's a lovely day for a flight, yes?
我叫艾格尼丝  有任何能为您效劳的地方
I am Agnes, and if there is anything that you need at all,
千万别客气哦[法国腔]
you can just let me know. Hmm?
好  好
Cool. Cool.
不要掉队好吗
Please don't lag behind.
我刚被长串法文轰炸了  我一句都没听懂
I just got french bombed, and I have no idea what she said,
我们应该是该给她小费吧
but I think we should tip her.
天啊  我真不敢相信
Oh, my God. I can't believe...
我又坐上私人飞机了
I'm back on a private plane.
麦克斯  超感谢你跟那个陌生人上床了
Max, thank you so much for having sex with that stranger.
乐意之极
Aw, it was my pleasure.
肉体超乐意哦
Literally.
欢迎上机  我是艾格尼丝
Welcome aboard, I am Agnes.
我帮你们放行李吧
I can take those for you.
您有需要放的行李吗
Do you have luggage?
在这里啊
Ah oui.
非常感谢  我是卡洛琳
Merci beaucoup. Agnes. Je m'appelle Caroline.
她是麦克斯
Elle est Max.
你真漂亮[音同朱莉]
Ah, vous etes tres jolie.
谬赞了  但我不是安吉丽娜·朱莉
Oh, thank you. I'm not Angelina Jolie.
常有人这么说
I get that a lot.
您的法语说得非常好呢
You speak french very well.
太棒了
Bravo!
一般人说法语时  用词是对的  但口音很重
Normalement, les gens ont les mots, mais avec un accent terrible.
但和您讲话就好象跟我妹妹聊天一样
Mais avec vous, c'est comme si je parlais avec ma soeur.
我不知道我是不是跟您妹妹说的一样好
Oh ! Je ne sais pas si je parle aussi bien que votre soeur.
但我敢说我比大多数美国人说得好
Mais je parle mieux que la majorite des Americains
他们只懂怎么用法语说
qui pense que le fracais est...
"薯条"
"Le french fry."
我就知道这一点
That's all I know.
只要你把我晾一旁跟她聊法语
And every time you ice me out with her,
我就会这么跟你玩
that's what's coming your way.
所以私人飞机的规矩是怎样
Okay, so how does this work?
需要票吗  我坐哪里
Do we need tickets? Where do I sit?
我不想害自己
Because I don't wanna embarrass myself
在法国空姐前丢脸
in front of french stewart.
麦克斯  这没有指定座位
Max, there are no seat assignments.
你想坐哪里都行
You can sit anywhere.
酷啊  跟戒酒会一样
Oh, cool. Like A.A.
我爱死G5私人飞机了
I love a G5.
这好勾起我家以前那台飞机的回忆
This reminds me so much of the plane we used to have.
等等  麦克斯  这飞机超眼熟啊
Wait, Max, this plane looks very familiar.
麦克斯  这就是我的飞机
Max, this was my plane.
现在是我的飞机啦
Well, it's my plane now.
-如果这真是我以前的飞机  -不是的
- Wait, if this was my plane... -Which it isn't.
这下面肯定会有我以前留着应急的东西
There'd be something I hid down here for an emergency.
钱  黄金  还是爆米花吗
Money? Gold? Kettle corn?
找到了  我的香奈儿唇彩
Yep. My Chanel lip gloss.
妈咪他妈了个哄
Abra-ca-damn-dabra.
你以前是亿万富翁
You were a Billionaire,
你留下的应急物品  是一根唇蜜吗
and for an emergency, you hid lip gloss?
为防天有不测风云嘛
Just in case something went wrong.
飞机真"下去"了  我也想看起来美美滴
I wanted to look good if I was going down.
只要你愿意"下去"  男人才不管你
you know they don't care what you look like
是美还是丑咧
as long as you go down.
我在犯什么傻啊
What the hell is wrong with me?
我居然像富家女那样擦唇膏
I'm glossing like a rich gal.
我得省着用  擦个两年啊
This has gotta last me two years.
你们要用毛巾擦手吗
Would you like a towel?
多少钱
How much?
麦克斯  那是免费的
Max, they're free.
就像戒酒会的免费甜甜圈
Oh, like the doughnuts at A.A.
天啊  烫死人了
Jeez, that's hot!
你应该先提醒老娘的
You should warn a bitch.
非常抱歉  她是第一次坐飞机
So sorry. It's her first time on a plane.
说了我每次都会这样
Every time.
再等一个乘客上机
We only are waiting for one more passenger,
我们就可以起飞了
and then we'll be departing.
来点香槟吗
Champagne?
非常感谢
Merci beaucoup.
我上一次喝香槟还是在逸林酒店
Ooh, the last time I had champagne
当时我混进一场菲律宾婚礼蹭吃蹭喝
was at a filipino wedding I crashed at a Doubletree.
还有一位乘客  会是谁呢
Another passenger? I wonder who it could be.
可能是我妈
Probably my mother.
每次当我人生中要有好事发生时
Every time something great is about to happen to me,
她总会半路杀出来毁掉它
she shows up and ruins it.
在短短的20小时  我们从在小巷里喝啤酒
In 20 hours, we went from beer in an alley
晋升到在飞机上喝高级香槟
to dom on a plane.
也算是奇迹了
That's pretty magical.
对啊  小日子不能更美好了
Yeah, this could not get any better.
麦克斯  现在变得更美好了
Max, it did just get better.
那是二链子 真是不敢相信
That's 2 Chainz. I can't believe it.
早上好  你们好吗
Good morning. How y'all doing?
好  好
Cool. Cool.
好的
All right.
二链子先生  早上好
Monsieur deux Chainz, good morning.
咖啡  水  还是香槟
Coffee, water, champagne?
不了  我很累  只想倒头大睡
No, I'm really tired. I just wanna crash.
不是咒飞机倒哦
Not the plane.
你们有什么睡睡茶吗
Do you have any sleepy time tea?
"睡睡茶"
"Sleepy time tea"?
感觉就超流氓范啊
That is so gangster!
飞机动了
Oh, we're moving.
麦克斯  把安全带系上  我们要起飞了
Max, buckle your seat belt. We're about to take off.
我有点害怕
I'm a little scared.
起飞是什么感觉啊
What's it gonna feel like?
就这样吗  那我还挺熟悉的
Oh, that's it? That feels familiar.
床头柜那根电动棒就是我的私人飞"鸡"
Guess I have a private plane in my nightstand.
我简直难以置信
I can't believe this.
我居然站在一个会飞的客厅里吃着火腿
I'm standing in a flying living room eating ham.
那是来自意大利的熏火腿
That's prosciutto from Italy.
这是来自那桌子的火腿
It's ham from right over there.
我准备加大火力消灭那盘火腿了
And I'm about to go ham on this ham.
都过了两小时了
It's been two hours.
二链子什么时候会醒呀  我想跟他合影
When is 2 Chainz gonna wake up? I want a picture.
你想让他醒来跟你合影吗
You want him to wake up for a picture?
我来搞定
I'll handle that.
醒了吗
Anything?
没醒  再来一次
Nothing. Do it again.
哇  那个睡睡茶还真让他昏睡过去了
Wow, that sleepy time really knocks you out.
他肯定是喝了"二"包
He must have two-bagged it.
他完全睡死过去了  咱们动手吧
He's totally out. Let's just do it.
慢着  我们只是要跟他合影
Wait, we're just gonna take his picture,
-除此之外没别的  对吧  -对
- nothing else, right? - Yes.
好  因为场面常常都会变得很失控
Okay, 'cause I can see how these things can get out of hand.
-好  我先来  -不不不  我先
- Okay, I'm first. - No, no, no, I'm first.
-我的飞机我说了算  -老实说  这是我的飞机
- It's my plane. - Well, actually it's my plane.
曾是你的飞机  现在是我的了
Was your plane. It's mine now.
我为了它  早晨做爱到腿抽筋呢
I had morning sex for it with a leg cramp.
等等  再拍一张  再拍一张
Wait, do another, do another.
这张好
Good one.
脸书默认新头像
New facebook default.
我要把这张照片设为我所有的默认头像
In fact, this is my new default pic for everything
包括我的墓碑照
including my tombstone.
既然你托胸  那我只有把屁股翘到他脸上了
Since you did boobs, I'm gonna put my booty in his face,
因为他生日最想要的是大屁股骚妞
'cause all he wants for his birthday is a big booty ho.
近点  我拍不下你们俩
Closer. I can't get both of you.
靠近点
Get closer.
被这样弄醒  再多次也甘愿
I never get tired of waking up like this.
二链子先生  真是太丢脸了
Oh, Mr. Chainz, I am so mortified.
我不是存心要打扰你  我只是想装酷而已
I didn't wanna bother you. I was just gonna be cool.
不打扰与装酷  早在拍下合影
Oh, that ship sailed with the butt pic
然后屁股撞到链子先生后就没可能了
and then crashed with "Mr. Chainz."
我只想跟你合影  因为我是你的超级粉丝
I just wanted a picture because I am such a huge fan.
祝你在今晚的格莱美奖上获奖
And I wanted to wish you luck tonight at the Grammys
因为你的音乐对我意义重大
because your music means a lot to me.
你的歌词超级能引起我的共鸣
And I totally related when you said
-* 我死后  请将我埋在古奇店里 *  -的确
- * When I die bury me inside the Gucci store * - True.
* 我死后  请将我埋在路易威登店里 *
* When I die bury me inside the Louis store *
* 我生日就要个大屁股骚妞玩玩 *
* All I want for my birthday is a big booty ho *
没错
Yeah.
各位  在搞什么派对呢
Hey, what's the party, players?
我听见"屁股"和"骚妞"了
I heard "booty" and I heard "ho,"
所以我必须得"插"一脚
so I had to do a pop-in.
派对的兴致总是被某些奇怪的白人给搞砸
Always some weird white guy coming to crash a party.
链子兄
Chainz.
不是吧  不可能
Stop. No way.
居然是你开这架飞机
I can't believe it's you flying this plane.
卡洛琳  好久不见
Caroline, it's been so long since I've seen you.
-过来抱抱  -麦克斯  这位是比尔
- Bring it in. - Oh, Max, this is Bill.
-机长  -机长
- The pilot. -The pilot?
为什么他在随意走动
Why is he walking around?
抓稳扶好  抓稳扶好
Brace for crash! Brace for crash!
没事的  现在是自动驾驶模式[放任自流]
It's okay, it's on autopilot.
放任自流  我的人生就是这样过活
Autopilot. That's how I live my life.
比尔机长是我的老朋友
Pilot Bill is an old pal.
在大学时  他经常载我和我朋友到处飞
He used to fly my friends and I around in college.
是啊  美好的时光
Yeah, good times.
这位是我的朋友  麦克斯
This is my friend, Max,
这是她第一次坐飞机
and it's her very first time on an airplane.
我也是
Hey, mine too.
开玩笑啦
J.K.
麦克斯  你何不往前走走
Listen, Max, why don't you take a stroll down there
-去驾驶舱看看呢  -驾驶舱[鸡鸡坑]
- and check out the cockpit? - The cockpit?
如果是像第14街的基佬吧一样
If it's anything like the gay bar on 14th street,
那我恐怕没穿对衣服
I'm not dressed right.
见到你真高兴
It is so good to see you.
天啊  我都忘了你有多漂亮了
And, god, I'd forgotten how beautiful you are.
谢谢  比尔机长
Oh, thank you, Pilot Bill.
我之前从来不觉得我可以高攀你
You know, I never thought I had a chance with you before
因为你家财万贯  而我又比你大20岁
because you had so much money and I was 20 years older,
但现在你破产了  而我做了拉皮整容
but now you're broke and I had a facelift,
所以我们现在算是同一等级了
so we're kinda on the same level.
拉皮整容啊
Oh, a facelift?
所以你的脸才看起来这么紧致粉嫩
That's why your face is so tight and pink?
我还以为你是火灾烫平了呢
I thought maybe you were in a fire.
但你看起来不错
But you look good.
-当然  我们可以约会  -太好了
- Sure, let's go out. -Great.
我要去拿杯咖啡  马上回来
I'm gonna grab a coffee. I'll be right back.
你怎么会跟这种人约会呢
What you doing going out with a guy like that?
我是有苦衷的  二先生
Well, here's the thing, 2.
你不能在飞机上告诉机长
You don't tell the pilot flying the plane you're on
你不想跟他约会
that you don't wanna go out with him.
理解
Got you.
那你在着陆前  好好跟他调情吧
You just keep flirting with him until we land.
我必须赶到今晚的格莱美奖
I gotta make it to the Grammys.
麦克斯  你以前真的没有坐过飞机吗
So, Max, you've really never been on a plane before?
严格来说  这是第二次
Well, technically it's my second time
如果嘉年华的翻转飞机也算的话
if you count rock-o-plane ride at the carnival.
可能当时我玩太猛了
Guess I was rockin' that plane too hard,
因为转到一半的时候
'cause halfway through the ride,
我的迷你飞机从支架上脱落
my mini-747 fell off its gears,
然后我就坠机了
and I crashed to the ground.
本来是要告他们的
There would have been a lawsuit,
但嘉年华管理员用一个甜筒收买我
but the carnie paid me off with a snow cone,
而且我小时候根本没人在乎我
and also no one cared about me as a child.
来吧  把你的手放在方向盘上
Well, go ahead, put your hands on the wheel.
-玩一下试试  -算了
- Give it a spin. - No, I'm good.
哇  我们飞得真高
Wow, we are really up there.
我从来没有这么高高地飞在天空
I have never been this high.
相信我  我嗑药[高飞]经验可多了
And trust me, I have been high.
我懂你的意思
Yeah, I hear that.
没有人比我更喜欢嗑药了
No one liked to get high more than me.
我什么都试过  药丸  大麻  可卡因
I did everything-pills, weed, coke,
把可卡因磨碎了撒在大麻上的那种叫啥来着
And what's that called when you crumble the coke on your weed?
总而言之  我无药不欢啊
Anyway, I loved to get high.
但是我现在不这样了
But that's all way behind me now.
看过丹泽尔的电影
I've been clean and sober
《迫降航班》后  我就戒毒并保持清醒了
ever since that Denzel Flight movie came out.
那电影现在还没下档呢
It's still in the theaters.
对啊  我上周看的
Yep, saw it last week.
或许我会把手放在方向盘上
Maybe I will put my hands on the wheel.
以防万一
You know, just in case.
嘉年华的坠机事件重现
It's the carnival ride all over again!
我把飞机弄坏了  我把飞机弄坏了
I broke the plane! I broke the plane!
没事  一切都在控制之中
Okay, everything's under control.
坐下坐下  把安全带系上
Just sit down, sit down. Put your seat belt on.
卡洛琳  这是我的电话
And, uh, Caroline, here's my cellular.
当然  你还能打电话去我妈家找我
Of course, you can always still get me at my mom's, so--
-快去拯救飞机  -好的  好的
- Go save the plane! - Yeah. Yeah.
没事的啦
We'll be fine.
我注定不会以一个跟班的身份
I was not meant to die as the second banana
死在横跨美国的约炮专机上啦
in a cross-country booty call.
天啊
Mon dieu mon dieu!
天哪 为什么在我遇她们的时候
Mais pourquoi ca m'arrive maintenant
发生这种事
jusque quand je rencontre ...
这不是真的
C'est pas vrai! Oh la la!
她刚说什么
What did she say?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我只听见"爱"和"为什么现在"
I heard "love" and "why now?"
我要以防万一
So just in case.
我一直没有告诉你  我从小蛋糕基金里
I should tell you I took $10 out of the cupcake fund
拿了10块钱去买巨无霸汉堡
for a big mac and never told you.
我也没告诉你  我为了让头发维持天然金
I should tell you I took $100 out of the cupcake fund
从小蛋糕基金里拿了100块钱去染发
to keep my hair this naturally blonde.
各位  飞机出了点小状况
Okay, everybody. We got a bit of a situation.
似乎我新女友的朋友把飞机弄坏了
Looks like my new girlfriend's friend broke the plane.
不是啦  我开玩笑的  是引擎出了问题
No, I'm just kidding. We had some engine trouble.
我们得在堪萨斯紧急迫降
We're going to have to make an emergency landing in Kansas.
加油  堪萨斯城酋长队[美式足球队]
Go, Chiefs!
金发妹
Hey, blondie.
为了不降落  你何不牺牲一下
Why don't you keep us in the air?
不如你去给那位机长一点"爱爱"
How about you go give the pilot a little love?
好的  好的  谢谢
Okay. Okay, thank you.
好消息
Well, good news.
我们不会被困在这里
We're not stranded here.
我刚通完电话
I just got off the phone,
我的新男友  拉皮机长说
and according to my new boyfriend, captain facelift,
你的新男友  那个英国人
your new boyfriend, the brit,
明天会安排我们坐民航飞机回家
is flying us home tomorrow on a commercial flight.
-二等舱哦  -什么
- Coach. - What?
人家坐不惯二等舱啦
I don't do coach.
而且我非常确定
And I am pretty positive
如果你没有在降落的玉米地  玩半小时说唱
2 Chainz would have taken us on that other plane they sent
二链子一定会带我们
if you hadn't rapped for 30 minutes
坐另外一架飞机去参加格莱美
in that corn field after we landed.
那只是你的一面之词
I don't care what you say.
我可是让那片玉米地都炸出了爆米花
I burned that corn field up.
来  吃点东西吧  他们送来了食物
Here, let's eat something. They delivered the food.
牛肉干  奶酪饼干  披萨口味薯片
Slim jims, cheez-its, pizza pringles,
还有两个火腿奶酪三明治
and two ham and cheese sandwiches.
火腿  我的意大利熏火腿呢
Ham? Where's the prosciutto?
没有
There is none.
为什么
Mais pourquoi?
因为我们是在堪萨斯的汽车旅馆里
Because we're at a motel in Kansas.
前台小姐因为我打电话说要披萨口味薯片
And the lady at the front desk called me a snob
而骂我做作装逼
for ordering the pizza pringles.
真不敢相信我没去成格莱美
I can't believe I'm not at the Grammys,
还被困在这里吃自动贩卖机的烂三明治
and I'm stuck here eating a lousy vending machine sandwich.
总比在餐馆摆弄番茄酱强啊
Well, it's better than doing those ketchups in the diner.
而且跟一位说唱界的巨星迫降在玉米地里
And crash-landing in a corn field with a rap star
咱俩还毫发无损
with our heads still attached-
也算是奇迹了  对吧
that's pretty magical, right?
对  二链子的确有说
Yeah, and 2 Chainz did say
他很高兴遇见咱俩个有爱的大屁股骚妞
he enjoyed meeting us and that we're two fine, big booty hos.
上天待我不薄啊
That's pretty magical.
要是阿憨知道
Han's gonna be so jealous
我遇见我们的偶像  一定会嫉妒死的
when he finds out I met our boy.
天啊  我们忘了帮阿憨的T恤签名了
Oh, my god, we forgot to get han's t-shirt signed.
是吗
Or did we?
当你没有钱弥补你犯下的错误时
When you don't have enough money to fix your own mistakes,
那就得靠自己创造奇迹
you've gotta make your own magic.
麦克斯  是二"链"子  不是二"愣"子啦
Max, it's 2 Chainz with a "z" not an "s".
靠  我唯一一次懂怎么写
Damn! The one time I know how to spell something,
结果还是让我出糗了
and it comes back to bite me in the ass.
颁奖典礼开始了
Ooh, it's starting.
准备好参加格莱美了吗
Ready to go to the Grammys?
火腿别沾到裙子
Don't get any ham on the dress.
我们得还回去退钱的
We have to return these to get our money back.
你觉得碧昂丝会说这种话吗
You think Beyonce's saying that right now?
如果我们可以创造自己的奇迹
Hey, if we can make our own magic,
那我们也可以创造自己的格莱美
we can make our own Grammys.
麦克斯·布莱克  你穿哪个设计师的
Max Black, who are you wearing?
你穿哪个设计师的
Who are you wearing?
这是"我室友租金牌"
My roommate's rent.
你说得对  感觉真奇妙
You're right, this is pretty magical.
慢着  我觉得还可以更妙
But wait, I think it can get better.
瞧
See?
超级妙吧
Way more magical.
这种感觉有点像私人飞机呢
You know, this kind of feels like the private plane.
对啊  我床头那根私人飞"鸡"
Yeah, the one I have in my nightstand.